BRIAN W. PETTY

application@bpetty.tech
https://linkedin.com/in/bwpetty
(765) 631-5080 | Anderson, IN | Open to Relocation

<u>CAREER SUMMARY:</u> After 10+ years in hospitality management, I went back to school and earned my Bachelor's in Information Systems Security, and I'm now looking to transition into the cybersecurity field. I'm currently completing my Masters in Cybersecurity Studies & I have earned my CompTIA Security+ and multiple AWS certifications.

EXPERIENCE

Full-time Graduate Student American Public University

Charles Town, WV June 2022 - Present

• Enrolled in Cybersecurity Studies degree program, which include studies of network security, information assurance, risk management, information security, cybercrime, and digital forensics. with the Master of Science in Cybersecurity Studies.

Concentrix Daleville, IN
Senior Technical Advisor June 2020 – August 2021

- Assigned to Tier 2 troubleshooting team, handing escalations and interfacing with engineering groups
- Functioned as team lead / Senior Advisor for all Tier 1 technicians overseeing mobile devices, desktop and laptop support, wireless devices, and multimedia devices, and served as a mentor to new technical support advisors
- Trained new staff in quickly & efficiently handling customer issues and complaints, using de-escalation and conflict resolution techniques

Continuum Anderson, IN

Customer Service Representative

June 2019 - October 2019

• Tier 1 technical support for mobile customers, as well as billing and account assistance, and customer service.

Various Hotels Marianna, FL

Multiple roles, including General Manager

April 2002 – June 2014

- Managed all aspects of hotel operations, from Guest Services to General Management
- Designed training for all new hires for multiple locations
- Completely modernized IT assets and network architecture, including re-cabling PoE Cisco Wi-Fi Access Points, as well as replacing and re-configuring the router and restoring Wi-Fi access to all of the hotel rooms and lobby, resulting in an approximately 30% surge in customer satisfaction
- Developed yearly business plan, performed all sales and marketing efforts, designed & managed multiple projects
- Cut costs reasonably and upgraded amenities, resulting in a 70% decrease in monthly costs, as well as an increase in guest satisfaction with offered amenities and programs, such as the daily breakfast.

CERTIFICATIONS

• CompTIA Security+ CE

- AWS Certified Developer Associate
- AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate
- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

EDUCATION

American Public University M.S. Cybersecurity Studies

Charles Town, WV Expected graduation date of June 2024

American Public University

B.S. Information Systems Security, Cum Laude

Charles Town, WV June 2020

COMPUTER LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

- Languages: Python, HTML
- Linux: Debian, RHEL, and Arch-based distributions
- Windows: Server and Workstation editions, Group Policies, and Windows Subsystem for Linux, Sysinternals, PowerShell, Windows Subsystem for Linux, WMIC, Firewall, and Registry
- Kali, Parrot, and BlackArch: bash, Wireshark, nmap, Metasploit, DirBuster, exploitdb, BurpSuite